<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>
	<string id="ui_mcm_menu_ballistics">
		<text>ArtiGrok Ballistics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_title">
		<text>ArtiGrok Ballistics - Merge & Extension of GBO and ArtiBalls</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_debug">
		<text>Developer logging.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_recycler">
		<text>"Recycler" Works for Ammo Breakdown?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_recycler_desc">
		<text>Turning this on will allow "Recycler" to give you a higher chance of getting more ammo materials back when breaking down ammo.\n 
		\nTurning this off will allow Ammo Maker to work normally.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_particles">
		<text>Special Ammo Particle Effects</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_particles_desc">
		<text>Certain special/variant ammo give off special particle effects when firing. Turn these off if they are too distracting when firing.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_npc_effect">
		<text>NPCs Use Ballistics System?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_npc_effect_desc">
		<text>Turning this on will enable NPCs to follow the same outgoing damage calculations that the player follows when hitting NPCs and mutants.\n 
		\nNPCs will not use any special ammo effects to avoid any crashes. This will also not affect NPCs hitting the player as that is handled seperately.\n 
		\nTurning this off will make NPCs' outgoing damage calculations return to normal.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_npc_use_special">
		<text>NPCs Use Special Effects? (UNSTABLE)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_npc_use_special_desc">
		<text>Turning this on will enable NPCs to utilize most special effects when hitting NPCs and mutants.\n 
		\nYou need ot have "NPCs Use Ballistics System" enabled.\n 
		\n%c[d_red]THIS MAY BE UNSTABLE - USE AT YOUR OWN RISK</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_true_falloff">
		<text>More Accurate Damage Falloff?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_true_falloff_desc">
		<text>Turning this on will calculate damage falloff utilizing the weapon's stats rather than it slowly starting immediately.\n 
		\nTurning this off will have damage falloff work as base GAMMA (with falloff starting immediately).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_difficulty_scaling_damage">
		<text>Enable Difficulty Scaling (Damage)?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_difficulty_scaling_damage_desc">
		<text>Turning this on will enable GAMMA's difficulty scaling on all outgoing player and (with the option enabled) NPC Stalker damage. This setting only allows scaling to affect damage (i.e. Hard reduces outgoing player damage/increases NPC-to-NPC damage by 20%).\n 
		\nTurning this off will turn scaling off, leaving damage untouched on all difficulties.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_difficulty_scaling_ap">
		<text>Enable Difficulty Scaling (AP/BR)?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_ballistics_difficulty_scaling_ap_desc">
		<text>Turning this on will enable GAMMA's difficulty scaling on all outgoing player and (with the option enabled) NPC Stalker AP power. This setting only allows scaling to affect AP power (i.e. Hard reduces outgoing player AP power/increases NPC-to-NPC AP power by 20%).\n 
		\nTurning this off will turn scaling off, leaving AP power untouched on all difficulties.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>